leasebusters.com 2005-05-25

# LeaseBusters - Canada's #1 Lease Takeover Pioneers

**Privacy policy**

In order to comply with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, Leasebusters has created a Privacy Policy and has designated an in-house Privacy Officer in order to assure all our clients and participants personal information is handled both appropriately and pursuant to the direction which was represented.

Leasebusters has several departments and business models that require personal information from clients and participants.  The extent of the personal information required varies from department to department.  The following business model breakdown will identify the information that may be required in order to successfully conduct business with Leasebusters

** Vehicle Sales/Vehicle Leases/Vehicle Finance Agreements**

  * Your name, address and telephone number

  * Email address and fax number

  * A credit card number

  * Personal banking information

  * Information of your driving habits (type of vehicle, kilometers driven annually etc).

  * Information of your existing vehicle(s) and any trade-in.

  * Details of your vehicle and its service history.

  * Your drivers license number

  * The name of your insurance company, policy number, agent and telephone number.

  * Your date of birth and/or date of birth of other members of your family

  * Your Social Insurance Number

  * Financial and credit information (specific information as set out in the application for credit documents).

  * The principle amount of your loan, interest rate and repayment schedule.

The personal information identified above may be used by Leasebusters to provide products and to perform services that are requested by you (the client).  We may also disclose this information to third parties such as financial institutions, credit reporting agencies, insurance companies and extended warranty agencies.  Your personal information will only be forwarded with your permission and direction pursuant to the products and services requested. 

** Lease-Take-Over (LTO) Pre-registration and Registration**

·         Your name, phone number(s) and email address

·         Your city of residence and postal code

·         Your current leased vehicle information (year, make, model, equipment level, etc)

·         The lease parameters attached to your vehicle.

·         The leasing company and original selling dealership information.

·         Any other pertinent information that will assist the Leasebusters LTO program in successfully remarketing your existing leased vehicle.

Upon retaining Leasebusters (formally registering) to remarket your vehicle, consult with prospective buyers and promote your leased vehicle, you have consented to the disclosure of the information described above to any party interested, verbally, on our website, as well as in any marketing media we may choose.

** Hot-Buyers List**

  * Your name, phone number(s) and email address

  * The city and province you reside in.

  * Information about the car(s) you are looking for, the desired monthly payment, the desired term and your timeline attached to acquiring a vehicle.

  * Your personal perspective about your credit rating.

By signing up on our hot-buyers list you are consenting to the display of some of your information on our website and receive information about the availability of vehicles that match your requested requirements.  Furthermore, you are consenting to allow Leasebusters sales representatives and or authorized agents and dealer affiliates to either electronically or formally (telephone) contact you with available vehicles that match your requested requirements.

** Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention**

The personal information that Leasebusters collects will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, unless the individual consents, or unless the use or disclosure is required by law.  Personal information will only be retained by Leasebusters long enough to fulfill those purposes or as required by law, after which it will be destroyed.

** Safeguards & Storage**

Leasebusters has security safeguards currently in place to ensure that personal information is not used or disclosed inappropriately.  All personal information we collect is stored securely and is accessible only by our staff as necessary to serve our clients.  Personal information is kept by us as required during ongoing transactions or as we are required to by tax or other laws.

** Privacy Statement**

Leasebusters is dedicated to protecting your privacy and safeguarding the personal information we collect.  Furthermore, we do not collect personal information without your consent.

** USE – A Final Overview**

Leasebusters may use the personal and financial information you supply to communicate with you, process applications and to provide the products and services you have requested.

Leasebusters only uses personal information for the purposes that we have disclosed to you.  If for any reason your information is required to fulfill a different purpose, we will first notify you and ask for your consent.

Only with your consent will we share information with associated businesses or suppliers who offer automotive related services or products which may be of interest to you.  Otherwise, we will not share personal information about you with other parties unless it is necessary to provide the services or products you request, or if we are required to do so by law.

If you would prefer not to receive information about special offers promoting our products and services, please let us know.

Information you provide us may be used to compile statistics which are non-specific to you and do not identify you, in order that we may improve our service to you.

** Questions, comments or concerns**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or about your personal information, you may contact our Privacy Officer:

  * Mr. Jim Matthews, General Manager

  * Phone number:  905-629-2270 Ext: 223

  * Toll Free:  1-888-357-2678 Ext:  223

  * Fax:  905-629-3299

  * Email:  [ jmatthews@leasebusters.com](mailto:jmatthews@leasebusters.com)
